{"data":[{"question":"The dentist gave me a check up and then telling me I needed two fillings.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"me","b":"check up","c":"telling","d":"fillings","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Telling-> to tell","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"These engines used being started by hand. But now they are started by electricity.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"used","b":"being","c":"But now","d":"are","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Used being->used to be","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"This house is often broken off and a lot of things are taken away.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"broken","c":"off","d":"away","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Off->in\/into\n-Break in\/into: to enter a building by using force, in order to steal something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"My father has a mechanic to repair his motorbike monthly.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has","b":"a","c":"to repair","d":"monthly","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- To repair-> repair\nHave somebody do sth\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"There always is one wise woman who is both feared and respected by her people.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"always","b":"wise","c":"who","d":"both","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Always is-> is always","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The woman tells them close their eyes tightly and cover them with their hands.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"tells","b":"close","c":"tightly","d":"with","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Close-> to close","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"They visited America about a thousand years ago, on the eleventh century AD.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"visited","b":"thousand","c":"ago","d":"on","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- On-> in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Ha Dong is the town where I am born and grew up.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"where","c":"am","d":"grew","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Am-> was","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"She is the girl about that I talked to you yesterday.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"the girl","b":"that","c":"to","d":"yesterday","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- That-> whom","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The lesson that we are learning now is very interested but difficult.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"that","b":"now","c":"interested","d":"but","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Interested-> interesting","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}